pythoncentral.io 2017-06-06

# Python Central Privacy Policy | Python Central

## Your privacy is critically important to us.

  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Python Central collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Python Central's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Python Central's visitors use its website.

Python Central also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Python Central uses cookies to help Python Central identify and track visitors, their usage of Python Central website, and their website access preferences. Python Central visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Python Central's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Python Central's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Python Central may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Python Central’s sole discretion. Python Central encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Third Party Advertising

Some of the advertisements you see on the Site are selected and delivered by third parties, such as ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers. These third parties may collect information about you and your online activities, either on the Site or on other websites, through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies in an effort to understand your interests and deliver to you advertisements that are tailored to your interests.

Python is a beautiful language.
